[Music]
Heat.
Heat
up here.
[Music]
insight. I think it was a fantastic idea
and and compliments to the team which
sort of ideated the idea this whole
session itself. Uh and I think we should
do more and more and celebrate all these
things. At the end of it the the culture
that we have to build and we are
constantly communicating and all of you
are responding is that ideas reside with
everybody. Good ideas reside with
everybody. better ideas resides with
with interface with the customers and
anybody who sees the pain or observes
the pain we must be able to as a bank
feed that in for product for tech for
designers for architects to build in and
make it I think each idea was a great
idea in terms of uh you know
implementation whether it's improving
the customer service adding to the
bouquet or uh uh you know really the uh
you know value proposition to the
customer so let's get cracking and look
forward for more such things in future.
I think this is fantastic. Yeah. What I
really liked about was the length and
breadth of the country from where the
ideas came from and virtually every
department. I mean so I think that is
what you know as you're moving from this
bank to bank tech or I mean the hasht23
overall initiatives I mean the larger
organization getting involved I hope
next time that 1,000 that you started
off becomes 10,000.
So I mean and I don't mind spending that
much more extra time because this is
really
[Music]
worth liked about